<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Island Sprite</title>
    <link>https://islandsprite.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Island Sprite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://islandsprite.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://islandsprite.com/plantir-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://islandsprite.com/plantir-privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Plantir Privacy Policy &amp;amp; Terms of use I take the privacy of my users very seriously, and do not collect any personal information that is not necessary for the app&amp;rsquo;s functionality.
Plantir can access some information (photos) for use in the app.
No data from the app is sent back to me or collected in any way. I don&amp;rsquo;t even know anything about your use of the app unless you email me for support and give me information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://islandsprite.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://islandsprite.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me  My name is Cameron Holiman and I love making things. I am a software developer and enjoy playing and collecting retro video games, making and drinking snobby coffee, watching Twitch, making props and hiking in my spare time.
My primary project is Plantir. An app to help manage your plants and keep track of their watering schedule (or fertilize, repotting, etc. Any type schedule really).
I also have a Coffee Snob Sicker app for iMessage if stickers are your thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apps</title>
      <link>https://islandsprite.com/apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://islandsprite.com/apps/</guid>
      <description>Apps Plantir Plantir is a plant organizer and management app. Easily keep track of all your plants and their tasks &amp;amp; schedules (watering, fertilizing, etc.) so that your plants can stay healthy and grow. See Plantir&amp;rsquo;s webpage for more info about it
 Coffee Snob Sticker for iMessage Do you like coffee? Becaues I sure do! That&amp;rsquo;s why I made these stickers.
They were even featured on MacStories!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
